Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
What's going on here?
Is this Prince Changfeng's psychic power?
Why is it so different from before?
His psychic power is strong,
but
it's also chaotic.
I'll make you lots of delicious chestnut cake.
I'll wait for my Changfeng to come home.
Killing her is ridding the nation of evil.
We must not let the Seven Stars Lamp extend her life.
Our soldiers died for the country,
yet that witch ceded land and paid reparations.
It's her.
Only if she dies
Seven Stars Lamp
As long as we steal this item,
she will die.
At least
she won't benefit from it.
Leave no survivors.
If word gets out,
we'll all be killed.
Is anyone over there?
No.
We can't expose the Lanhai Society.
No one can be left alive.
Seven Stars Descend upon the Child
He really didn't lie to me.
Who?
The one who killed you and Qin Yu.
Who is it, really?
It doesn't matter.
As long as we stop that witch from living longer,
nothing else matters.
Only if she dies
can the dynasty be saved.
Our lifelong goal is right before us.
I won't let you ruin all of this.
For that vague, unreachable goal,
you're willing to die so foolishly?
Over there.
Yes.
What about your grandmother?
You haven't come home in over ten years,
and now you're on the run.
Only now do you remember her.
You brought pursuers because of this,
putting your elderly grandmother
in danger.
Prince Changfeng,
you're unfilial,
and unjust.
Talking about grand ambitions,
pretending to be a man of ideals.
My grandmother is just a woman.
Those soldiers won't do anything to her.
Such an excuse—
do you even believe it yourself?
Changfeng,
why are you leaving so soon?
Wait a little longer.
Grandmother's chestnut cake will be ready soon.
I've already said,
it's urgent, I must leave right away.
You—
why insist on making chestnut cake?
Look at you,
after all these years,
you finally came home once,
but you're still hiding.
You won't even let me
tell anyone you've come home.
Be honest with your grandmother—
did you do something wrong out there?
Grandmother,
even if I told you, you wouldn't understand.
I'm acting for the people's sake,
it's a deed that will be remembered forever.
Anyway, you don't need to worry.
I have to leave now.
The pursuers will be here soon.
There are pursuers.
It's my fault as your grandmother.
I shouldn't have nagged.
Go quickly, go quickly!
Don't let them catch up.
Go now!
Grandmother,
if they come,
just tell the truth—
I came back suddenly,
but you know nothing else.
You're just an old lady.
Those soldiers won't do anything to you.
Don't worry.
They—
how could they harm an old woman like me?
Go quickly!
Be careful on the road.
Take care.
Go now!
Be careful.
Be careful on your way.
Safe travels.
Do you know why your grandmother
is so obsessed with chestnut cake?
As expected,
a casual remark you made as a child
became her lifelong wish.
From now on, every year at this time,
I'll have to eat grandmother's chestnut cake at home.
Alright.
When you grow up,
you'll have more things to do,
no time to come home
and keep this old lady company.
I defend our home and country
so you won't suffer through war again.
Your peace and happiness
matter more than anything.
Alright then.
Every year when this season comes,
I'll make you lots of delicious chestnut cake.
I'll wait for my Changfeng to come home.
Grandmother,
it's me, Feng'er, who is unfilial.
I can only repay your kindness in the next life.
Does it feel comfortable?
No need to wait for the next life—
you can see her right now if you go down.
What do you mean?
Your grandmother, last night,
hanged herself to death.
You lied to me.
My grandmother has always been healthy.
She
She was always busy,
smiling all day long,
a
an old lady.
How could she suddenly hang herself?
How could she suddenly do that?
You lied to me.
I didn't lie to you.
That's right.
She wouldn't hang herself for no reason.
After you left yesterday,
she received another guest.
The room was tidy and clean.
No signs of a struggle.
He seemed like a polite guest.
He came this time
just to ask about your whereabouts, Shen Changfeng.
He wouldn't press too hard,
but he wouldn't give up easily either.
And your grandmother?
What would she think?
To protect you,
what would she do?
Some things
aren't what I wish for either.
I never thought someone like Brother Changfeng
would be treasured by someone.
Protected with their life.
She made an excuse
and went into the room alone.
She put on the burial clothes she'd prepared.
She straightened her clothes
and quietly set off.
Eat more.
You child...
Grandmother.
I'm sorry.
You, you...
It's fine, it's fine.
Grandmother.
You rascal.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Let me lie down too.
Your grandson is going to join the army.
I don't know when I'll be back.
Grandmother.
I'm sorry.
Forgive Changfeng for being unfilial.
Get up.
You, you...
Grandmother.
Changfeng is sorry to you.
It's the old lady's spirit and energy.
But Shen Changfeng,
you can't die yet.
You still haven't told me
who killed you,
who killed Qin Yu,
and who killed your grandmother.
Tell me.
At this point,
you're still stubborn, aren't you?
I don't know his identity either.
He's very mysterious.
I only know he's a cultivator...
A cultivator...
You're here.
Grandmother.
I'm sorry.
You, you...
Still the same as when you were little.
Let's go.
Fuyi.
What's wrong?
It's nothing, Fuyi.
There are others.
There are other clues.
There will be more people.
Last time in the carriage, you said I was seeing things.
What about yesterday?
We all saw it with our own eyes.
So...
Does Xiao Wuzi like you?
Logically speaking,
yes.
I knew it.
And you?
I don't know.
They're here.
Why is no one here?
Just like this.
Who dares to come in?
Eat quickly.
Stop making eyes.
Fuyi doesn't know if she likes you yet.
Just eat.
Yesterday.
How did you get hurt yesterday?
Are you okay?
What happened exactly?
Actually...
Yesterday, I caught up with that person.
Why don't you dare to speak?
Are you afraid I'll hear your voice?
Chase...
That person could fly.
He could overpower you.
That means his skills are top-notch.
He escaped unharmed from a cliff.
His agility is also unmatched.
A master like that
should be famous across the land.
That's right.
Such a master
There are very few in the world.
I don't know.
How does he compare to Daoist Yun Yi?
My master...
His skills are a bit better than yours,
but his agility is average.
Can't compare to that person.
It's still a gain.
Next,
we can search among the world's masters.
Little brother,
you have no idea.
Although
I didn't see that person's
face clearly,
but I saw the back of his head,
and I felt an aura of immortality.
That's exactly it.
It's just so
so
otherworldly.
Yes, just otherworldly.
Still otherworldly.
Wait,
is that person an immortal?
You better believe it.
That person's immortal aura
might mean
he's a Daoist.
Anyway,
we're close to the truth now.
And no matter who it is,
I won't let him
hurt you.
Here it comes—
Xiao Wuzi's romance mode.
Reporting to Prince,
a message arrived from the palace by carrier pigeon.
By order of the Empress Dowager,
we are to escort the Prince
and Miss He back to the palace for an audience.
We respectfully ask the Prince to depart at once.